Welcome to ConvertICO - where file formats
finally make sense.
My name is Alex, and I'm a filmmaker
with a confession to make.
I once spent three hours trying to open
a subtitle file in a calculator app.
In my defense, the file was named
"numbers.srt" - very misleading.
But then I discovered ConvertICO.com
and everything changed.
Now I convert subtitle formats
faster than I can misspell "entrepreneur."
This is my story.
This is The Subtitle Chronicles.
Chapter One: The Day Everything
Went Horribly Wrong.
It started with a phone call from the boss
at 6 AM on a Monday.
Nothing good has ever started with
a phone call at 6 AM on a Monday.